Dreams are not lived on the sidelines
Invincible is a drama, history film directed by Ericson Core.
Inspired by the true story of Vince Papale, a man with nothing to lose who
ignored the staggering odds and made his dream come true.
When the coach of Papale's beloved hometown football team hosted an unprecedented open tryout, the public consensus was that
it was a waste of time – no one good enough to play professional football was going to be found this way.
Vince Papale, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Dick Vermeil, played by Greg Kinnear.
Janet Cantrell, played by Elizabeth Banks.
Frank Papale, played by Kevin Conway.
Max Cantrell, played by Michael Rispoli.
Susan Vermeil, played by Morgan Turner.
Invincible is a 2006 American biographical sports
drama film directed by Ericson Core.
It is based on the story of Vince Papale (played by Mark Wahlberg), a bartender who became a member of the Philadelphia Eagles
in 1976 with the help of his coach, Dick Vermeil (Greg Kinnear); Elizabeth Banks and Michael Rispoli also star.
The film was released in the United States on August 25,
2006, receiving generally positive reviews.
The film explores themes of philadelphia, pennsylvania,
advancement, sports, american football, bad luck.
The tone is emotional.